[Day 3]
My gosh!
We're so glad you're back!
Yes.
- We're so glad you're back. - It's a new day.
Welcome back, Francine!
I'm here. I'm back, guys.
Happy.
I’ll make it up to you guys.
Hello!
Oh my God.
Oh my God!
Nice to meet you.
Welcome, everyone!
Come on in, come on in.
[1 hour ago]
Oh, here it is.
The menu.
Okay, sinigang.
So it’s a soup.
Palabok.
Inasal.
Salt-crusted sea bream.
Okay.
Got it.
Okay, now the uniform.
Oh, it’s pretty.
Okay.
Great.
Shouldn’t I put something in here?
Like a pen?
A pen and a menu, like this.
Isn’t this how they do it?
Is this how they do it?
Right here?
Put it in like this.
Alright.
Do we have a new staff?
He’s quite handsome, right?
Can you boss him around, Chef?
- Hello, hello! Hi! Hi! Hi! - Oh my gosh.
Hello!
How are you?
Good, nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Oh my God!
Hello!
Hello! Hi!
- Hi, nice to meet you. - Come in.
- I’m shy. - So how do we...
It feels awkward to move.
Hey, we’re shy.
Give us time to breathe!
- We'll breathe. - Oxygen!
It’s like I’m the owner here.
How are you guys feeling today?
Good!
Good, yes.
But...
It's weird because you're Korean and you're here.
How about you? What will you do?
Yes, what?
Server.
Server!
Ah, you’ll help us.
Kam-sam-hamnida.
It’s “Kam-sa-hamnida.”
What did I say?
“Kam-sam-hamnida.”
Oh my God!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm not usually like this.
I had my Korean correct last night.
But now I'm kind of like,
losing my words.
Okay, I will go to the kitchen.
Okay.
Thank you.
Welcome to Kumusta.
He ate the Rebisco.
Jodi, we’ve got someone to share it with.
[Kumusta]
[Kumusta] [Full House]
Since I had some part-time work when I was younger,
I think I can do this well.
That's very good. That's very nice.
Okay, so, this is our station.
This is the menu.
Okay.
This is where we get the order.
So after getting the order,
we have to give this...
yellow paper inside the kitchen.
Fighting, I’ll do my best.
Okay.
So...
Should we start working?
Yes.
How are you?
How’s our new employee?
Our new employee is handsome.
He’s handsome?
Is he kind?
Mhm.
He seems nice.
Mm-mm.
Jodi!
Yes?
It feels easier.
I have a companion.
It's faster.
In my opinion, I think I’m...
- Francine? - Yes?
I think I’m a bit better at this than Francine.
Ji?
Yes?
It's time for us to open.
Would you want to open the signboard outside?
Okay.
Let me do that.
Thank you.
We’re open!
Open?
Thank you!
Kitchen! We're open!
Okay.
I'm sure the guests, they'd be like,
“Oh my gosh, he's here.” Right?
Yeah.
- Welcome! - Hi!
- Welcome! - Oh my gosh!
Hello!
Nice to meet you.
Oh my God!
Please sit wherever you like.
Is it possible to sit here?
Yes, you can sit here.
Thank you!
This will be your menus.
This one is for you.
This one is for you, ma’am.
I’ll get your water.
Isn’t he so handsome?
What do you wanna eat?
Pick whatever you wanna eat.
Could you recommend something kid-friendly?
- Oh, recommendations? - Yes.
It’s my first day today.
- Oh really? - Yes.
What kind of...
They’re usually not picky.
- Oh, is that so? - Yes.
- How about some fish? - Yes!
Oh, do you like fish?
- Should we order the fish? - Yes.
Do you wanna get this inasal?
Then we will...
Let’s get what the handsome uncle recommended.
One fish, one inasal.
Do you want your desserts after your meal?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
One inasal,
one fish,
one just rice,
one halo-halo.
Halo-halo!
Okay.
One what?
Fish and inasal.
Okay.
And rice.
Yeah.
Hello!
Welcome!
- Hello! - Yes!
For two, please.
You can sit wherever you like.
You’re so handsome.
Thank you.
This is our welcome drink. It’s calamansi juice.
Thank you!
Can you give us some recommendations?
That’s the hardest question.
It’s actually my first time today.
My first day.
What do you suggest?
We’ll get what you wanna try.
We’ll try it for you.
If it were me...
I was actually kinda curious about kare-kare.
Me, too.
- Kare-kare? - Yes.
- One inasal, one kare-kare. - Rice, too.
Do you want one garlic rice as well?
Thank you.
Okay.
What did they want?
One inasal, one kare-kare,
one garlic rice.
Kitchen.
Kitchen, okay.
She's bossing me pretty well, huh?
Chef!
Yes!
He’s too handsome.
Seriously, are you out of your mind?
I can’t stop looking at him, what do I do?
You’re risking your life for a celebrity you won’t see again.
You’re risking your life!
He’s handsome. What can I do?
Hello!
Hello.
Why is he here?
I’m a part-timer here for today.
- Are you here for a meal? - Yes, yes.
Okay, here you go.
Here you go.
He looks better in person.
He’s handsome.
This is our welcome drink. It’s calamansi juice.
Thank you.
- We’ll order. - Okay.
- This one. - Palabok?
- This one. - Inasal.
And garlic rice.
Oh, okay.
But the inasal takes around 15 minutes.
That’s okay.
- How about your drinks? - Drinks? We’ll see.
Okay, thank you.
He’s handsome.
Chef!
One palabok,
one inasal,
one garlic rice,
one gising-gising.
Okay.
Alright. Okay.
Fish, inasal,
I think kare-kare was next.
And then, he said inasal again.
And then...
So, these are the sequence of the order.
Look, J, in this order.
So basically, the gising-gising came in last.
- Okay? - Okay.
Okay! Let's go, kare-kare.
[Kare-kare]
[Kare-kare] [A rich Filipino stew of]
[Kare-kare] [pork offal and vegetables]
[Kare-kare] [cooked in a thick, savoury]
[Kare-kare] [peanut sauce]
Okay, so just one scoop.
Beef stock.
Just small amounts.
Okay, I'm gonna plate this.
Looks good!
[Today’s Menu: Kare-kare]
Hi!
So this is your kare-kare
and your garlic rice.
Garlic bap!
Bap, bap!
- It looks so good! - Try it.
How is it?
Is it good?
It’s so delicious.
- Which part of meat is this? - I have no idea.
Some of these are new to me.
Are these innards?
Oh, it’s good!
Right?
This is goated.
Ji, inasal!
And rice.
There you go. Thank you.
Here’s your inasal.
Thank you!
Did he say gamasal?
Inasal.
Mina?
Ina!
I-na-sal!
This is beautifully cooked.
Ji, Table 1 with the baby.
Am I supposed to pour the sauce over or dip it?
One moment, please.
How do you...
Do you pour the sauce?
What is?
Oh, okay, so...
You can either pour it,
or dip.
- You can pour it or dip it. - Whatever I want, okay.
You can also dip.
Okay, thank you.
Do you wanna dip it?
Mom, I think we should pour it.
It was cooked nicely.
Hi, this is your gising-gising and palabok.
It’s good if you eat the two dishes together.
Hello!
Welcome!
I think they’re Filipinos.
We’re five, and we have one baby.
We’re six in total.
Yes, they’re Filipinos.
Ah, Filipino?
Yes!
Do you need... hello!
Do you need a baby chair?
Yes please, one chair.
Okay, please come in.
Okay, for the baby.
Ah, for the baby please. Thank you.
Okay.
I’ll just get water.
Hello!
Jodi is so slim.
But her face is cute.
They said, “Jodi Sta. Maria is so slim.”
Do I look fat?
I don’t know.
This is our welcome drink, calamansi juice.
It’s good.
Yummy?
Is it sour?
Excuse...
Excuse me, we’ll order.
Yes?
One palabok, one inasal,
and one kare-kare.
Four plain rice
and one garlic rice.
Ah, two garlic rice.
Three plain rice.
Three plain.
- Two garlic rice. - Okay.
I’m excited for the inasal.
It’s been ages since I had inasal.
Okay.
One more inasal.
Shortcut as hell.
Kare-kare, ready.
Kare-kare!
Is it ready?
For Table 5.
Here’s your kare-kare.
- Did you order this? - Put it in the middle, please.
Alright, in the middle.
Thank you so much!
- Thank you! - Excuse me.
Are you from Korea or just visiting?
I’m from here, and they’re visiting me.
Oh, that's so sweet!
I’m the eldest, and they’re my family.
Okay.
Alright, enjoy. I won’t disturb you anymore.
Thank you.
This actually contains beef tripe and by-products.
There’s beef tripe in it.
Yum.
It’s delicious, right?
And this one, it’s really delicious.
Oh okay, noodle? Okay, okay.
More?
Oh my God, this is it!
Right, it’s delicious?
It’s so tasty.
Here’s your inasal.
Thank you.
Is that the inasal? It looks good.
I think this is atchara.
Wow! So good.
Very tasty.
- What? Inasal? - Inasal.
Jodi, I’ll deliver this, okay?
Okay!
Where should this missing inasal go?
Uhm... missing inasal?
Ah, the one with another inasal.
- Inasal..? - Which table?
Um, another inasal?
For what table?
Everything is...
Everything is checked.
[All Inasal Served]
[Inasal Made By Mistake]
I think we confused everything with everything.
Yeah, no one ordered for another inasal.
No more inasal for any table.
It’s mine.
You ordered this?
Yeah.
It’s good!
So it's your order?
Yes, yes, that’s right.
Everything’s my fault.
Ah! He’s eating it!
Wait.
Vinegar.
Soy sauce.
Korean chilli powder.
[Jodi: Working Hard]
[Ji: ]
[Ji: Eating Harder]
[Francine: Working Hard]
Ah, this is better with rice.
Thank you.
I’ll get the others.
[Ya!]
Hey Oppa!
Back to work!
No lunch time yet.
She’s small but terrible, huh?
What’s “oppa”?
Older brother.
[Oppa: Working Hard Again]
Hello.
It’s our last call for orders.
Is there anything else you’d like to order?
- Can we get one more of this? - Yeah, go ahead.
Might as well have one more palabok.
One more palabok.
Okay.
Oh, it’s so yummy.
Seriously, this is the first time I’ve liked palabok.
It’s delicious!
It’s delicious. It’s not oily.
Um, chefs?
Table 5 wants one more palabok.
- One more palabok? - Yes.
Okay.
You know what to do, right?
Uh-huh.
[Falling to you palabok]
Chef, one palabok.
Oh my God, our first order.
Palabok is ready.
Hi, serving your palabok.
Delicious!
Delicious?
Thank you!
Short and sweet.
It's heartwarming for me to see
how much they like the food that I helped prepare.
So, yeah. It's crazy.
Maybe I have a future with palabok.
Maybe.
I’m full.
Ah, I’m so full.
That was good.
That was really good.
Be good.
Be good, boys and girls.
[04:00 PM]
[04:00 PM] [Break Time]
What do you usually eat here during lunch?
Sometimes I eat Korean street food, like tteokbokki.
Or I just cook something simple, like ramyun.
[The Iconic Korean Ramyun]
Oh, ramyun sounds good.
Okay, then I’ll cook you guys some ramyun
and make it a little less spicy.
Just relax for a bit, and I’ll bring it right out.
Ramyun, please!
Ramyun, ASAP please!
Yes, I’ll bring it right away.
[Korean Expert, When She’s Hungry]
Since she asked for ramyun ASAP...
Ramyun...
I can’t look at…
It’s actually hard to look into his eyes.
Why?
Are you melting for him?
You melt so fast, huh?
Such a softie!
Chef, you’re so soft.
Chef is a softie!
I think I’m just tired.
[Chef Ji - The Ramyun Master]
Oh, it's there!
Wow!
Chef, can you tell us if it's super spicy?
Okay.
Let’s eat.
Thank you.
Thank you for cooking for us.
Enjoy your meal!
It doesn’t look super spicy.
Let's see.
It’s spicy!
But okay.
This isn’t too spicy for you, right?
Perfect.
Good.
Oh, thank you.
The noodles, you cooked well.
Not overcooked. It's al dente.
Oh, thank you.
Chef, can I have more?
Me too. I want.
Chef, can I have one more?
Actually, I saw Chef at the airport.
[Their Unexpected Encounter] We met.
No, because when I saw you,
I saw your friend in the airplane.
And he went like this to me.
And I'm like, "Oh, Korean people know me?"
Wow!
- Oh, wow! - I made it already?
To Korea?
Your friend.
He went like this.
And I'm like, "Oh, maybe because of the tattoo."
And then, destiny.
And now...
See?
- Photo, photo, photo. - Picture, picture.
AHHHHH!!
Oh my God!
Oh my God, I can’t believe it!
No way!
Chef, I can’t stand you.
Oh my God!
I'm sorry.
I used my hand.
Ah, it’s okay.
I just... just... just the hand.
I'm not gay.
I'm married!
I truly believe
he's a secret admirer.
Sorry to kiss you.
I got caught in the moment.
Okay.
Hey.
Round 2.
Light it up.
It's like you're warming up the car.
Maybe I'll...
You know what? I'll pre-cook some fish.
Hey, Jodi.
Yes!
For tonight, I only have two portions of fish.
Okay.
[1 day ago] We have a new dish today, right?
[1 day ago] Salt-crusted.
[1 day ago] Yes.
How many?
[Bought Out The Entire Store...] 15 pieces.
[Bought Out The Entire Store...] Thank you.
Table 8!
One sea bream...
One sea bream, one garlic rice...
There’s fish again!
Oh, three fish!
[Limited Stocks Only!]
[Limited Stocks Only!] I need to make one more.
[Limited Stocks Only!] Wow.
Okay.
And that was...
That's it.
And that's it?
Please tell everyone that.
Okay.
Ji.
We only have two portions of fish.
We cannot accept.
Got it.
I think we’re ready?
We're opening the restaurant.
Okay, open.
Dinner service
starts now.
We’re open!
Let's go!
Alright!
Hi!
Hello! Welcome!
[Off to a Good Start with one Guest]
Hello.
[Oops! She’s not alone..?]
Table for how many?
We’re six.
Six.
Oh, if you’re six…
Take your time,
and call me when you're ready.
Okay.
FYI, there's a large group
- Okay, I see. - that just came in.
Large group.
Large.
Six.
Definitely there's gonna be an inasal.
Okay, inasal is ready.
Should we get one of each?
Yeah, that should work.
- Then this, this, and this? - Yes, one of each.
- Sounds good. - One of each.
- We'll get one sinigang. - Okay.
One palabok and one inasal.
Is it okay if we order a lot?
Yes, of course.
Then one garlic rice.
Thank you.
This one, Janella. It has numbers already.
So,
one sinigang, one palabok, one inasal, one fish,
one kare-kare,
- Okay. - one garlic rice.
- Alright. - That’s a lot.
[Here comes the second group]
Hello! Welcome.
Wait, I just snorted.
Hello, table for three.
Three? You can sit anywhere you like.
I think I wanna be here.
Would you like to sit here?
Table for two?
Could you give us some recommendations?
We’re hungry.
- Are you hungry? - Yes.
If you want something quick,
sinigang or palabok comes out pretty fast.
We’ll get...
this one and this one.
Three of these, please.
One rice,
two San Miguel, and one Coke Zero.
Okay, got it.
Thank you.
How long will this take?
Well...
It depends on the chef’s mood...
Chef’s mood? Hahaha!
He better be in a good mood today.
[In His Best Mood Today!]
[In His Best Mood Today!] Just put the fish in again.
Oh!
Oh, it’s good! Wow.
If I refill this 10 times,
- You can keep seeing him. - do I get to see him 10 times?
When I go to restaurants with friends,
I usually just look at them,
but now I can’t stop looking at him.
I wanna keep ordering.
I can't help but smile.
He’s driving me crazy.
So...
Sinigang.
Sinigang is boiling and it's ready.
Okay.
We can do this.
Sorry.
I just need to add soup.
Soup.
Okay.
Sinigang is ready.
Palabok is also ready.
Okay.
I’ll work on the inasal.
This is beautifully cooked.
Inasal ready!
So, kare-kare.
Sauce.
There you go.
And then... this.
Kare-kare is ready!
Okay.
Table 5.
Sinigang.
Hello! This is your sinigang.
Chicken and your palabok.
Okay, it's your kare-kare.
- Kare-kare? - Yes.
Thank you.
I’m excited because we ordered a lot.
Mmm~
- This is delicious. - Is it good?
I gotta try it.
It’s delicious.
Since it's not too spicy or anything...
Everything suits our taste.
I think everyone will enjoy it.
You're right.
[3rd Customer In]
[4th Customer In]
[5th Customer In]
Hello.
Inasal and two San Miguel, please.
- Two San Miguel? - Yes.
Palabok.
Salt-crusted sea bream.
Okay.
We are going to have these four.
Okay, thank you so much.
Thank you.
Four is done.
Hello!
[Never-Ending Customers!]
[Limited Seats Almost Full!]
This is your welcome drink. It’s calamansi juice.
Calamansi juice?
- Wow! - Thank you so much.
We are ready.
We will order one...
kare-kare.
And then we will have one palabok.
Two inasal.
And one gising-gising.
Chef!
Yo.
One palabok, one inasal...
One palabok, one inasal
Wow.
A lot of inasal.
Palabok!
Table 1 ordered quite a lot.
We can do this!
We can do this.
Let's go, team!
Tim Yap.
Can be!
Can be, can be, can be, can be.
Uncle Tim is still relevant!
Hello! Welcome.
Hello.
- Table for two? - Yes, two.
[No More Table For Two]
[No More Table For Two] We’re out of seats right now.
[No More Table For Two] What should I do?
- Is the round table okay? - Yes, yes.
Let’s sit there.
Take your time, and let me know when you're ready.
[Full House]
[Orders Rushing In!] One, two, three, four, five...
[Orders Rushing In!] We are getting slammed.
Oh...
I'm running out of plates for inasal.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, I’ll wash the dishes.
Gotcha.
We ordered this earlier. How much longer will it take?
Inasal takes a while. I’ll check it out for you.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Our kare-kare hasn’t come out yet.
- Could you check, please? - Sure, I’ll check.
Sorry, Table 7 is asking about the kare-kare.
Oh my gosh.
Stressed.
Yeah, this is the busiest...
Okay, so sinigang.
Ay, sinigang.
What’s going on?
Okay, palabok.
Okay.
Palabok!
Here’s your palabok.
I don’t have plates for kare-kare.
Can I just put one kare-kare here?
Just add more sauce.
Okay.
You can make it half full.
Yeah, half full.
Kare-kare!
Sorry, the kare-kare took a while.
No, it’s okay.
Sorry for the wait.
Oh, no worries.
Wow!
Two more palaboks.
Kare-kare.
Gising-gising.
Okay.
I'm gonna make the gising-gising first.
Gising-gising!
Here’s your gising-gising.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Why? What happened?
How long time? Inasal?
Inasal?
How many inasal in total? Four?
This one, one minute.
Ah, one minute?
Then three...
Seven minutes.
Ah, seven minutes?
Really?
“Really?”
Don’t “Really?” me.
I will...
Okay, let's go.
Let's do this well.
Chin, here’s the inasal.
For table..?
I don’t know. I just know I owe four.
Okay, inasal up!
Hi, this is chicken inasal.
How is it?
- It’s so good. - Really?
Oh, the smell.
This tastes like galbi.
I think inasal is my favourite.
It’s so good.
Really nice.
Taste like home.
My gosh.
Right? It’s really authentic.
Yeah.
Baby, is it yummy?
Yummy!
Inasal, Table 4?
Table 4?
Table 3.
Table 3?
I think Table 3 is done.
Wait a second, Oppa.
Has this... not been served yet?
- The one you ordered. - No, it came out already.
Oh, this isn’t it? Ah…
Who got here first?
The heck?
I think this came out by mistake.
Oh, I’m sorry.
- Chicken, we... - I think that’s ours.
We did order it, but...
I’m so sorry.
I noticed it.
Is this for Table 6?
Okay, no palabok for Table 6.
Table 4 is done.
Tables 1 and 3 are done.
Okay, this is Table 9.
Hello, did you order for another garlic rice?
No.
No? But this is your palabok.
Palabok, okay.
- Yes. - Thank you.
Garlic rice, maybe...
There.
Table 6?
Table 6.
Okay.
Did you order another garlic rice?
Oh, yes.
Yes, we did.
Here.
Fish is up!
Ay, this one.
Table 3.
Ah, okay.
I believe this is our last fish.
- Wow. - Enjoy your meal.
The fish tastes good on its own.
It melts in your mouth.
Is it good?
Mmm, delicious!
Jack.
That’s the last fish.
Oh last fish? Yeah, you’re right.
It took them like several days.
Pacific ocean.
He wants fish but it’s sold out.
Gosh, that’s the main dish.
Should we ask for a bite?
Is the sea bream good?
It’s good.
Do you want some?
Oh really?
- We can give you some. - Really?
Then just a bit. Just one piece.
Thank you, oh my God.
Yeah, if you try...
We’ll give you more if you like it.
We don’t usually do this. This is our first time.
- I’m sorry. - No worries.
It’s good! It’s tangy.
- Mmm~ - It’s delicious, right?
It’s my first time getting food from the other table.
I know right.
Thank you.
Let’s go?
Oh, shoot.
Wait a minute.
Can we get the bill, please?
Yes, one moment please. 14,000 won...
- We’re a bit old-school, so... - You can take your time.
Hello, welcome!
[New Customers Enter]
[Still No Vacant Table]
[And Still Cleaning Up]
Are you fine with a round table?
Yes.
Would it be okay for you to sit here?
- Oh, are there three of you? - Two.
Oh, two? Then please take a seat here.
[Solo Diner]
Three people in one table.
So we have three people in one table.
So you might get confused with multiple Table 9.
But the number is written on top.
In order.
I don't know what to do.
You okay?
Yeah, just overwhelmed.
But you have a very good energy.
So, that matters a lot.
Some people break.
You're not.
I try, I try.
Thank you.
[New Customers Again]
[New Customers Again] Four?
[New Customers Again] You wanna sit here?
Here's your menu, and then I'll just prepare your plates.
Thank you.
The food was so good.
Wow, inasal?
Welcome your customer!
[Seo In Guk - Singer & Actor]
Let me ask,
how did you find out about this?
Since this is Korea,
I heard you need the help of a Korean.
So I rushed over immediately when I heard the news.
Because in order to serve Korean customers,
you need someone like me for a smooth operation.
So I’ll do my best.
My goal is to work very hard here
and buy this building.
Huh?!
Oh, okay.
But thank you very much.
We really need help.
Because we're really having trouble with...
Your presence here is
very much needed and
we know that you are very busy
but you really took the time to be here.
So I just want to say from all of us here in...
Oh my gosh.
I’m okay, gwenchana!
Okay.
No, really, I'm okay.